H. Alexander Smith Papers, 1897-1966 (bulk 1920-1966 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 4: Senatorial Career, 1931-1958; 159.67 linear feet 376 boxes
  - Subseries 4E: Public Issues, 1944-1958; 59.21 linear feet 142 boxes
    - 1957, 55 boxes (1 partial)
      - Ireland, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Jaa-Jac, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Jae-Jay, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Japanese Letters, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Je-Jof, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Jencks Case, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Jewish, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Jewish, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Jewish, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Jewish, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Joh, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Johnson and Johnson, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Joi-Jol, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Jones, Walter, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Jor-Joy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Judiciary Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Justice Department, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Kaa-Kan, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Kalmuk, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Kap-Kay, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Kea-Kei, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Kel, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Kem-Kep, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Ker-Key, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Kia-Kim, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Kin-Kiz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Kl, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Kn, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Ko, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Korea, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Kr, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Ku-Ky, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Laa-Lam, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Labor Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Labor, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Labor Department, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Lamb, Barney, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Lan-Lap, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Las-Law, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Lay-Led, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - League of Women Voters, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Lee-Lei, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Lel-Les, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Let-Lev, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Letters of Introduction, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Lew-Lie, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Library of Congress, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Lif-Lin, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Lincroft Acres, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Day Dinner, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Square Project, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Lio-Liz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Lists, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Livestock, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Loa-Lom, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Lon-Lou, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Long Branch Armory, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Lounsbury, Ralph, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Lov-Lou, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Low Flying Planes, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Luf-Luz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Maa-Mad, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Mae-Mal, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Man-Map, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Maple Crest Development, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Maps, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Mara-Marr, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Mas-Mat, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Mau-May, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - McA-McCl, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - McCarthy, Senator, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - McCo-McCu, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - McE-McG, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - McGuire Air Force Base, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - McH-McK, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - McKee, Frederich C, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - McL-McO, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - McP-Meh, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Mars-Mary, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Mei-Mel, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Mer-Mes, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Meriweather Post Music Contest, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Meu-Mey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Mia-Milk, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Milk, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Milk Industry, Bloc Voting Co-Ops, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Milk Industry Correspondence, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Milk Digests and Agricultural Bulletins, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Milk Industry, Digests Re-Hearings, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Milla-Mille, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Milh-Milw, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Min-Miz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Minority Peoples, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Moa-Mol, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Modern Republicanism, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Mon-Moo, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Mora-Moro, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Morr-Mory, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Mos-Moy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Motor Carrier Leases, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Mua-Mul, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Mullins, Marjorie A, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Mum-Mun, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Mus-Muz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Na, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - National Science Foundation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - National Academy of Science, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - National Grange Building, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - National Guard, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - National Health Survey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - National Institute for Advanced Study, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - National Labor Relations Board, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Natural Gas Pipelines, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Navaho Missile Program, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Naval Shipbuilding Data, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Navy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Nea-Nev, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Negro File, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Nevada Horses, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - New, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - New Jersey, 1957; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - Additional Federal Judgeship, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Disaster Areas, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Citizens’ Committee for Hoover Reports, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - Farm Bureau, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
        - Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Potato Situation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Poultry, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Republican Party, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - State Chamber of Commerce, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Taxpayers Association, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Turnpike, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Water Shortage, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Newark Airport, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Newark Post Office Envelopes, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Newspapers and Magazines, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Newspapers and Magazines, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Newspapers and Magazines, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Newspapers and Magazines, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - New York Shipbuilding Corp, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - New York Naval Shipbuilding Employees, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Newa-Ney, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Ni-Noo, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Nixon, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Nor, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization Conferences, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Nos-Ny, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Oa-Oe, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Of-Ol, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Office of Defense Mobilization, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Om-Or, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Os-Oz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Paa-Pap, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Pakistan, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Par, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Parsippary, Troy Hills, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Pas-Pay, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Paterson Chamber of Commerce, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Pea-Pem, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Peiper, Colonel Joachim, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Pen-Pep, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Pes-Pey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - P’Eylim, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Pf-Ph, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Philadelphia Naval Shipyard, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Pi, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Pl-Pok, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Pol-Por, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Polls and Questionnaires, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Portsmouth Naval Shipyard, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Pos-Pow, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Post Exchanges, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Port of New York, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Post Office, Building Leases, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Post Office Department, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Post Office, Survey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Pra-Pre, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Princeton Post Office, General Files, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Princeton University Conference on NATO, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Pro-Py, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Q-Ram, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Questionnaires, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Racketeering, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Radio, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Rahway River, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Railroad Folder, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Railroad Fares, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Ran-Ray, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Raritan Arsenal, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Rate Flight, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Rea-Ree, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Reduction in Force, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Reed, E. B, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Ref-Rei, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Refugee Program, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Rel-Rh, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Republican Congressional Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Republican National Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Republican Policy Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Republican Regional Conference, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Republican Women’s Conference, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Reservoirs, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Reuther, Walter P, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Ria-Ric, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Rid-Ril, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Rin-Riz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Roa-Rob, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Roc-Rof, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Rog-Rop, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Theodore Roosevelt Island, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Rosa-Rose, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Rosi-Rov, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Route 22, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Row-Rum, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Run-Ruz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Russia, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Saa-Sai, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Saddle Brook Ranch, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Sak-San, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Salk Polio Vaccine, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Sap-Say, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Satellite, American, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Satellite, Russian, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Sca-Sce, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Sche-Schi, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Schl-Schm, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Schn-Scho, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - School Contracts, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - School Construction, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Schr-Schu, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Schw, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Sci-Scu, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Scrap Folder, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Sea-Sei, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Sek-Sey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Senate Gallery Passes, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Senatorial Campaign, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Senatorial Campaign, Backers, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Sergeant at Arms, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Sergeant at Arms, Floor Pass, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Seymour, Florence, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Sha-Shd, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - She-Shh, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Shi-Shp, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Sia-Sil, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Siegrist, Bob, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Sim-Sin, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Simkin and Sons, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Sip-Sl, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Slovak Folder, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Smith, New Jersey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Personal, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Smith, H. Alexander, 1957; portions of 2 boxes
        - Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Autographs and Pictures, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Face the Nation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Fifty-fifth Wedding Anniversary, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Leading Questions, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Office, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Pictures, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Smith, I-Z, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Sm-Sn, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Small Business, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - So, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Soil Bank, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Southern New Jersey Developmental Council, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Spa-Spe, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Spanish, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Speech Folder, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Spi-Spy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Staa-Stan, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Standard Metropolitan Areas, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Stap-Stee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - State Department, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Stationary, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Stef-Step, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Ster-Stev, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Stew-Stey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Sto, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Stony Brook, Millstone Watersheds Association, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Strategic Metals, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Str, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Stringfellow, George E, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Stu-Sty, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Studbaker-Packard Corporation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Su, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Sugar, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Summit Conference, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Superliners, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Supreme Court, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Supreme Court, California and New Mexico Communists, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Supreme Court, DuPont Anti-Trust, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Supreme Court, Jencks Case, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Supreme Court, Watkins, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Surplus Foods, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Sw-Sy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Syrian Jews, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Ta, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Tank Facilities, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Te-Thi, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Television, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Television, Toll, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Teterboro Airport, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Textile Plants, New Jersey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Textile Problems, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Tho, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Thr-Thy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Tin, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - To, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Tr, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Transportation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Treasury Department, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Trenton, Old Post Office Building, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Tu-Ty, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Tuna Fish, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - U, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Union-United, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Ukrainians, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Ukrainians, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - United States Information Agency, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - United Nations, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Urban Renewal and Slum Clearance, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Urban Watersheds, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Va, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Vacation and Holiday Trust Funds, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Van Nostramd, D, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Ve-Vi, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Vietnam, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Veterans, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Vineland Radio Station WWB2, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Vo-Vy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Waa-Wak, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Wage and Hour, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Wala-Wall, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Wallworth Apartments, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Walm-Wap, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - War, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Was-Way, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Watkins Decision, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Wea-Weh, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Wei, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Wel-Wen, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Wes-Wey, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - West Shore Railroad and Ferry, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Wha-White, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Whi-Why, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Wheeler, Airman, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - White House, Requests and Tours, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Wia-Wig, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Widnall, William B, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Wila-Wilk, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Will, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Wilm-Wilz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Wim-Win, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Winter Olympic Games, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Wir-Wiz, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Woa- Wom, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Woo, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Wolverton, Charles A, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Wor-Wy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - X-Y, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Yugoslavia, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Z, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Agriculture, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Agriculture, Cotton, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Agriculture, Price Supports, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Agriculture, Surplus, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Air Force, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Airlines, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Airports, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Alaska and Hawaii Statehood, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Alcoholic Beverages in Planes, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Alien Property, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - American History Month, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Antarctic, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Anti-Monopoly Hearings, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Appropriations, 1957; 14 folders
        - Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Agriculture, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Business Defense Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Defense Department, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Dental Research, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Economical Development and Technical Assistance, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - Flood Insurance, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
        - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
        - Juvenile Delinquency, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
        - Labor, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
        - Post Office, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
        - Slum Clearance, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 25)
        - State Department, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 26)
        - United States Information Agency, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Arabs, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - U.S.S. Arizona, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Armed Services, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Atomic, Nuclear, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Banking, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Billboards, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Bricker, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Bruce’s Eddy Dam, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Budget, 1957 June; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Budget, 1957 May; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Budget, 1957 April; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Budget, 1957 March; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Budget, Farm Journal Article, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Bulk Mail, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Burke Airport, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Buy American, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Civil Aeronautics, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Chaplain’s Day, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Cigarettes, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Civil Defense, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Civil Rights, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Civil Service, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Civil Service Pay, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Civil Service Retirement, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Cloture, Officials and Special Friends, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Cloture, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Coal, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Columbus Day, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Commissaries, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Communists and Communist Countries, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Compulsory Retirement, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Constitution Day, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Cotton, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Cranberries, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Deepening the Delaware, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Defense Department, Supply and Service Administration, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Deficiency Appropriation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Depressed Areas, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Dinosaur Park, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Disarmament Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - District of Columbia, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Draft Age, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Dulles, John Foster, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Educational Exchange, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Egyptian Jews, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Egypt and United Nations, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Eisenhower, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Electoral College, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Equal Rights, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Equality of Opportunity, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Exports, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Ex-Presidents, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Federal Administration Practice, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Federal Aid to States, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Federal Construction Contract Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Federal Employees, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Federal Grants in Aid, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Federal Housing, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Federal Home for the Aged, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Federal Housing Down Payments, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Federal Housing and G. I. Loans, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Federal Housing, Trust Funds, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Federal Pay Raise, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Federal Pay, Unscheduled Overtime, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Fifty-Fifty Shipping, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Fifth Amendment, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Financial Institutions, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Finger Printing Aliens, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Fish, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Fish and Wildlife, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Flood Control and Insurance, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Fluoridation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Foreign Aid, Including Appropriations, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Foreign Competition, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Foreign Policy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)